Yep, craziest outfit I've ever worn. I've never been scared to wear an outfit but
today, today with this outfit, 14 kilogram of catsuit and mask and gloves, yeah I'm
scared today. I partnered up with Ronya and I actually planned to wear this as a
really really extravagant carnival outfit but it arrived after carnival so
So today is going to be the day I'm going to try it on for the very first time.
So besides the mask I have gloves, a latex outfit, leather accessories and a 10kg back
entry silicon catsuit.
And this is super, super heavy.
I have no idea how I am going to wear this.
Send help, please.
First on my to-do list, put a lot of water-based lubricant inside.
I'm not going to show the dressing part because I've done it in another silicone catsuit video.
And also, I'm going to be cursing a lot.
So, I'll see you in a minute or 20.
I'm honest, I had help getting into this because it is a struggle with the boobs.
they're so heavy and I would highly recommend getting help so now I need to dress at least a
little bit okay I put some clothes on it's basically just a latex beanie set and after
I'm done wearing the latex I'm going to clean it properly so the silicone doesn't um yeah damage it
Anyway, it is heavy. I mean, and it bounces, which is the most fun part. Actually, even when I walk, the boobs bounce, which is pretty fun.
I don't know how it'll feel after I don't know half an hour hour but I can
already feel the weight on the shoulders because I mean it's 10 kilo when do you
normally wear an outfit that weights 10 kilo but I think it looks so funny I put
shiner on top of it I use the Smitheson silicon shiner which you can order at
to run your smithson shop and yeah that's why it's shiny so i'm going to continue putting this
outfit together because i'm not done next stage the leather accessories and over knee boots
and i mean the suit is formally meter thick i realized when i closed the over knee boots that
there is a bit more circumference than usually so the additional eight millimeters make things
harder not gonna lie and there's a bit of loose skin here but I think you can barely notice that
it's a bit too wide it is one size so I think compared to my other Smithersen Orion silicon
catsuit this one is smaller next up are the gloves they're really long and they do have
black painted fingernails not gonna lie i had a picture of them on my camera roll and it gave me
the creeps to see this picture like that because they look super realistic i don't know check this
anyway loop time again yummy it's cold so
since they're so long i put a bit of it on top of the suit
and now
try to get into them
It does not help that my other hand is squishy too.
Oh yeah, here we go.
Be careful with long sharp nails not to damage the silicone. I mean it's more durable than latex
I'd say because it's formerly me too thick but still be careful. Alright now I'm wearing them
so if you have any questions write them down in the comments I'll try to answer them. If you have
really really specific questions I always encourage you to write the manufacturer an email and ask them
because they know best and I also have a discount code for Rania and their sister
company Smitherson I will write it down in the description text as well so you
should check that out if you want to try something like this this is a bundle but
you can also buy the single pieces and as you can see it's also really stretchy
and right away the boobs have silicone filling and they're like flat on the
inside so my natural boobs push them out a bit more even and they're still bouncy so much fun
by the way this is g cup i think there's smaller ones available so why didn't i get them and even
bigger ones and after putting that on i can totally say this is not for beginners so you
should have at least experience with latex neck entry catsuits or even with other silicone catsuits
because it is a lot to get into it and also it's a lot to handle. This is like an experience you
can't really describe or find somewhere else. You have to try it yourself. It's really something
unique and I've never done something like this before. So next up is this one, the mask.
And I am going to wear a wig cap underneath because silicone and hair does not match well.
It is really a pain to get stuck in silicone with your hair.
So I don't know how much I can talk with the mask on.
I'm going to show it to you now and maybe not talk much later on.
You can also see the inside.
So it's full of silicone.
done. Yeah, let's try this. Oh my god. This is crazy. I mean, I can see myself with the
tiny holes in the eyes. It's a costume. I don't look anything at all like myself. I
don't know how good you can actually hear me. There's a mouth opening there in all the
and my lashes are a bit too long I can't really open close my eyes unless I pull
the mask a bit away from my face like this so I can open and close the eyes I
can also see better like this it also gives me posing vibes this is crazy
So there's lacing in the bag to close the mask.
And now for the last step, I do have a wig.
This is the wig.
But I don't think it looks that good.
Also, I'm going to stick my hair in it all the time.
And so it comes off again.
well that was
need to breathe first fresh air that was an experience
um i mean you can't breathe there are holes in the nose and in the mouth
but it's still it's restricting would I go out celebrating on carnival like that
no I would not definitely not would I wear it with the mask over a longer period of time
probably not it's just not my jam I don't feel really comfortable with it but I mean maybe it
is your jam anyway I'm glad to have my face in the open again if you want to see more silicon
catsuit content check out my patreon because I will always upload behind the scenes and additional
pictures there and leave a thumbs up in the comments write down how you like the outfit
would you wear something like that? Let me know. Maybe half a year ago I would have said no I'm
not going to wear something like this but here I am. Again check out my discount code with
Royana and Smittleson and thanks for watching this. I hope you saw something new today. I definitely
did something new today. Anyway have a nice day. See you around. Bye.